A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Offices xFA116
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Field Offices - Ankara, Turkey, 1968-1978; 19; 8 Cubic Feet 16 document cases 202 files
  - General files, 2
    - International Potato Center (CIP), 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 127)
      30.1, 30.5
    - International Potato Center (CIP), 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI), 1972 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - Iran, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 130)
      30.11
    - Iran, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 131)
    - Iraq, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 132)
    - Israel, 1972-1975 (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - Kenya, 1972-1977 (Box 11, Folder 134)
    - Lebanon, 1970-1975 (Box 11, Folder 135)
    - Libya, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - Loegering, William Q., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 137)
      Loegering was Professor of Plant Pathology at the University of Missouri.
    - Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 138)
      40.14
    - Netherlands, 1971-1977 (Box 11, Folder 139)
      30.10
    - Pakistan, 1971-1975 (Box 11, Folder 140)
      30.13
    - Rodenhiser, H.A., 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 141)
      20.8
    - Rupert, Joseph A., 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 142)
      20.5
      Rupert was a research associate with the Agronomy Department of the University of California, Davis, and with the International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center. He had previously served as an associate director with the Rockefeller Foundation's agriculture program in Chile.
    - Saari, Eugene E., 1971-1972
      Saari was a Plant Pathology expert with the Ford Foundation in India and then in Lebanon (from mid-1973).
      - 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 143)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 144)
    - Saudi Arabia, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - Stubbs, R. W., 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 146)
      Ron Stubbs was affiliated with the Institute of Phytopathological Research in the Netherlands.
    - Stubbs, R. W., 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - Turkey: General
      15
      Incoming and outgoing correspondence may be separated within the files.
      - 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 148)
      - 1972 (Box 12, Folder 149)
      - 1973 (Box 12, Folder 150)
      - 1974 (Box 12, Folder 151)
      - 1975 (Box 12, Folder 152)
      - 1976 January-May (Box 12, Folder 153)
      - 1976 June-December (Box 12, Folder 154)
      - 1977 (Box 12, Folder 155)
      - 1978 January-May (Box 12, Folder 156)
      - 1978 June-December (Box 12, Folder 157)
    - Turkey: Istanbul, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 158)
    - United Nations Development Program (UNDP), 1973 (Box 12, Folder 159)
      40.37
      General
      One item.
      "Country and Inter-Country Programming: Turkey." UNDP assistance requested by the Government of Turkey for the period 1973-1977. Official Draft, January 1973.
    - United Nations Development Program (UNDP), 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 160)
    - United States: General
      20
      - 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 161)
      - 1972 (Box 13, Folder 162)
      - 1973 January-May (Box 13, Folder 163)
      - 1973 June-December (Box 13, Folder 164)
      - 1974 January-May (Box 13, Folder 165)
      - 1974 June-December (Box 13, Folder 166)
      - 1975 (Box 13, Folder 167)
      - 1976 January-June (Box 13, Folder 168)
      - 1976 July-December (Box 14, Folder 169)
      - 1977 (Box 14, Folder 170)
      - 1978 (Box 14, Folder 171)
    - United States: Universities (General)
      - 1976 (Box 14, Folder 172)
      - 1977 (Box 14, Folder 173)
      - 1978 January-August (Box 14, Folder 174)
      - 1978 September-December (Box 14, Folder 175)
    - United States: Kansas State University, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - United States: Michigan State University, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 177)
    - United States: Oklahoma State University, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 178)
    - United States: Oregon State University
      20.6-20.7
      Incoming and outgoing correspondence is generally separated within the files.
      - 1970 (Box 14, Folder 179)
      - 1971 (Box 14, Folder 180)
      - 1972 (Box 14, Folder 181)
      - 1973 January-June (Box 15, Folder 182)
      - 1973 July-October (Box 15, Folder 183)
      - 1973 November-December (Box 15, Folder 184)
      - 1974 January-May (Box 15, Folder 185)
      - 1974 June-December (Box 15, Folder 186)
      - 1975 (Box 15, Folder 187)
      - 1976 January-May (Box 15, Folder 188)
      - 1976 June-December (Box 15, Folder 189)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 190)
    - United States: Washington State University, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 191)
    - United States Agency for International Development: General
      15.4
      - 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 192)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 193)
        Only one item from 1973.
      - 1975 (Box 16, Folder 194)
    - United States Agency for International Development: Afghanistan, 1970-1974 (Box 16, Folder 195)
      30.8
    - United States Agency for International Development: Afghanistan, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 196)
      Report of Survey and Recommendations on Agricultural Research in Afghanistan, by Agricultural Research Review Team, 1972 October 25.
    - United States Agency for International Development: Morocco, 1970, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 197)
      30.7
    - United States Department of Agriculture (Beltsville, MD), 1970-1975 (Box 16, Folder 198)
    - Winkelmann, Donald
      40.34
      Winkelmann was an economist for the International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center.
      - 1972-1973 July (Box 16, Folder 199)
      - 1973 August - 1974 (Box 16, Folder 200)
    - Yemen, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 201)
    - Yugoslavia, 1971-1975 (Box 16, Folder 202)
      30.9